{"_id":"6a28f84818467851b6ec7807","id":"429","name":"Side Table","category":"Living Room","condition":"Older","posted_by":"23789","zipcode":"94102","date_added":1677715200,"age_days":1100,"age_years":3.01,"description":"This side table has been a convenient spot for lamps and books...","image":"/images/side-table.jpeg","comments":[{"author":"Ethan Wilson","comment":"This side table is the perfect size for my small living room. It adds a touch of modern style without taking up too much space. The built-in drawer is a bonus for storing odds and ends."},{"author":"Avery White","comment":"Love the versatility of this side table! It's perfect for holding my morning coffee, displaying a lamp and some plants, or even doubling as a small workspace. The sturdy construction and beautiful finish make it a great value."},{"author":"Isabella Thompson","comment":"This side table is a charming addition to my bedroom! The unique design and antique brass finish add a touch of personality to the space. It's the perfect spot for my reading lamp and a cozy blanket for snuggling up with a good book."}]}
